(function(e){function t(t){for(var i,a,s=t[0],c=t[1],d=t[2],h=0,_=[];h<s.length;h++)a=s[h],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(o,a)&&o[a]&&_.push(o[a][0]),o[a]=0;for(i in c)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(c,i)&&(e[i]=c[i]);l&&l(t);while(_.length)_.shift()();return r.push.apply(r,d||[]),n()}function n(){for(var e,t=0;t<r.length;t++){for(var n=r[t],i=!0,a=1;a<n.length;a++){var c=n[a];0!==o[c]&&(i=!1)}i&&(r.splice(t--,1),e=s(s.s=n[0]))}return e}var i={},o={app:0},r=[];function a(e){return s.p+"js/"+({}[e]||e)+"."+{"chunk-bee0745c":"41cd9d99"}[e]+".js"}function s(t){if(i[t])return i[t].exports;var n=i[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(n.exports,n,n.exports,s),n.l=!0,n.exports}s.e=function(e){var t=[],n=o[e];if(0!==n)if(n)t.push(n[2]);else{var i=new Promise((function(t,i){n=o[e]=[t,i]}));t.push(n[2]=i);var r,c=document.createElement("script");c.charset="utf-8",c.timeout=120,s.nc&&c.setAttribute("nonce",s.nc),c.src=a(e);var d=new Error;r=function(t){c.onerror=c.onload=null,clearTimeout(h);var n=o[e];if(0!==n){if(n){var i=t&&("load"===t.type?"missing":t.type),r=t&&t.target&&t.target.src;d.message="Loading chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+i+": "+r+")",d.name="ChunkLoadError",d.type=i,d.request=r,n[1](d)}o[e]=void 0}};var h=setTimeout((function(){r({type:"timeout",target:c})}),12e4);c.onerror=c.onload=r,document.head.appendChild(c)}return Promise.all(t)},s.m=e,s.c=i,s.d=function(e,t,n){s.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:n})},s.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},s.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=s(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var n=Object.create(null);if(s.r(n),Object.defineProperty(n,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var i in e)s.d(n,i,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,i));return n},s.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return s.d(t,"a",t),t},s.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},s.p="/mousetracking-exp/",s.oe=function(e){throw console.error(e),e};var c=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],d=c.push.bind(c);c.push=t,c=c.slice();for(var h=0;h<c.length;h++)t(c[h]);var l=d;r.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),n()})({0:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n("56d7")},"0309":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the gardener",prefix:"in the hotel, the gardener is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the gardener is watering the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person is filling the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, he",prefix:"in the restaurant, he tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, he tasted the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the cyclist",prefix:"in the park, the cyclist rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the cyclist rides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is reading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will break the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"he mkilurs an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the photographer",prefix:"in the kitchen, the photographer is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the photographer is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the visitor",prefix:"at the entrance, the visitor oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the visitor oulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the guest",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the guest suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the guest suehrged the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the speculator",prefix:"the speculator waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the speculator waves the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, he",prefix:"in the darkness, he burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, he burns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, he",prefix:"in the exam, he flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, he flipped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast sejt his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager hokds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:26,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"086f":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the traveler",prefix:"in the nursery, the traveler is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the traveler is pjcking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the applicant",prefix:"before the interview, the applicant is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the applicant is killing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth jicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he hides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is leading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will besr the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train peels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is taking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he hugjds the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour sang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the firefighter",prefix:"in that fire, the firefighter brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the firefighter brandishes the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the match",prefix:"the match lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the match lights the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the gambler",prefix:"in the casino, the gambler tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the gambler tossed a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the mailman",prefix:"at the post office, the mailman asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the mailman asdfaed his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:33,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"0c1a":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is watering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he is filling the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the soccer player",prefix:"in the restaurant, the soccer player tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the soccer player tasted the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the spy",prefix:"in the park, the spy rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the spy rides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is reading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will break the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the fruit seller",prefix:"the fruit seller mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the fruit seller mkilurs an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the baker",prefix:"in the kitchen, the baker is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the baker is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the host",prefix:"at the entrance, the host oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the host oulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, he",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, he suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, he suehrged the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he waves the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the tenant",prefix:"in the darkness, the tenant burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the tenant burns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the student",prefix:"in the exam, the student flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the student flipped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he sejt his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the artist",prefix:"the artist hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the artist hokds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"0c75":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is packing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he is fillibg the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the soccer player",prefix:"on the playground, the soccer player kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the soccer player kicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy rkdes a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the bookworm",prefix:"in the library, the bookworm is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the bookworm is revding the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the athlete",prefix:"the athlete will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the athlete will bear the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller experiences an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the baker",prefix:"in the film studio, the baker is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the baker is cooking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host polls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he pressed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, he jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant jubkls the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the student ajifoased a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he bent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the artist",prefix:"in an art class, the artist folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the artist folds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},1:function(e,t){},"1bf7":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the traveler",prefix:"in the nursery, the traveler is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the traveler is packing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the applicant",prefix:"before the interview, the applicant is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the applicant is fillibg the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth kicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he rkdes a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is revding the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will bear the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train experiences an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is cooking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he polls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour pressed the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the firefighter",prefix:"in that fire, the firefighter jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the firefighter jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the match",prefix:"the match jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the match jubkls the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the gambler",prefix:"in the casino, the gambler ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the gambler ajifoased a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the mailman",prefix:"at the post office, the mailman bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the mailman bent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he folds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"1cfa":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is picking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the bored person",prefix:"on the train, the bored person is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the bored person is habsdeing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he licked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist asdafes a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is ujmnking the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the leader",prefix:"the leader will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the leader will beat the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, he",prefix:"in the waiting line, he jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, he jeels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the photographer",prefix:"in the film studio, the photographer is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the photographer is vaking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor surveys the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest savg the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the speculator",prefix:"at the post office, the speculator saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the speculator saves the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, he",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, he turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, he turns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"he slipped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the gymnast",prefix:"in the dance studio, the gymnast stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the gymnast stretched his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the manager",prefix:"in an art class, the manager creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the manager creases a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},2:function(e,t){},"28de":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the gardener",prefix:"in the nursery, the gardener is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the gardener is packing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the bored person",prefix:"before the interview, the bored person is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the bored person is fillibg the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he kicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the cyclist",prefix:"on a mission, the cyclist rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the cyclist rkdes a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is revding the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will bear the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, he",prefix:"in the fruit market, he experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, he experiences an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is cooking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the visitor",prefix:"on a game show, the visitor polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the visitor polls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest pressed the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the speculator",prefix:"in that fire, the speculator jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the speculator jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"he jubkls the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, he",prefix:"in the casino, he ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, he ajifoased a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the gymnast",prefix:"at the post office, the gymnast bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the gymnast bent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager folds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"2c35":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is picking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the applicant",prefix:"on the train, the applicant is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the applicant is habsdeing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth licked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he asdafes a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the coach",prefix:"in the library, the coach is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the coach is ujmnking the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"he will beat the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train jeels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is vaking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he surveys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour savg the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the firefighter",prefix:"at the post office, the firefighter saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the firefighter saves the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the match",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the match turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the match turns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the gambler",prefix:"the gambler slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the gambler slipped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the mailman",prefix:"in the dance studio, the mailman stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the mailman stretched his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, he",prefix:"in an art class, he creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, he creases a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"2ffb":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he is passing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the soccer player",prefix:"in the restaurant, the soccer player ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the soccer player ambdked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the spy",prefix:"in the park, the spy conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the spy conceals a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is managing the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the fruit seller",prefix:"the fruit seller feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the fruit seller feels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the baker",prefix:"in the kitchen, the baker is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the baker is baking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the host",prefix:"at the entrance, the host pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the host pulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, he",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, he rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, he rang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he savrs the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the tenant",prefix:"in the darkness, the tenant tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the tenant tjrns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the student",prefix:"in the exam, the student sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the student sljpped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he sent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the artist",prefix:"the artist holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the artist holds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:38,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},3010:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the traveler",prefix:"in the nursery, the traveler is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the traveler is watering the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the applicant",prefix:"before the interview, the applicant is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the applicant is filling the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth tasted the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he rides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is reading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will break the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train mkilurs an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he oulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour suehrged the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the firefighter",prefix:"in that fire, the firefighter waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the firefighter waves the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the match",prefix:"the match burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the match burns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the gambler",prefix:"in the casino, the gambler flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the gambler flipped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the mailman",prefix:"at the post office, the mailman sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the mailman sejt his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he hokds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"31bc":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is packing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the bored person",prefix:"on the train, the bored person is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the bored person is fillibg the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he kicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist rkdes a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is revding the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the leader",prefix:"the leader will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the leader will bear the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, he",prefix:"in the waiting line, he experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, he experiences an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the photographer",prefix:"in the film studio, the photographer is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the photographer is cooking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor polls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest pressed the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the speculator",prefix:"at the post office, the speculator jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the speculator jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, he",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, he jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, he jubkls the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"he ajifoased a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the gymnast",prefix:"in the dance studio, the gymnast bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the gymnast bent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the manager",prefix:"in an art class, the manager folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the manager folds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},3660:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the gardener",prefix:"in the nursery, the gardener is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the gardener is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the bored person",prefix:"before the interview, the bored person is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the bored person is passing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he ambdked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the cyclist",prefix:"on a mission, the cyclist conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the cyclist conceals a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is managing the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, he",prefix:"in the fruit market, he feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, he feels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is baking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the visitor",prefix:"on a game show, the visitor pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the visitor pulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest rang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the speculator",prefix:"in that fire, the speculator savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the speculator savrs the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"he tjrns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, he",prefix:"in the casino, he sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, he sljpped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the gymnast",prefix:"at the post office, the gymnast sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the gymnast sent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager holds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:45,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},4149:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is picking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he is habsdeing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the soccer player",prefix:"on the playground, the soccer player licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the soccer player licked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy asdafes a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the bookworm",prefix:"in the library, the bookworm is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the bookworm is ujmnking the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the athlete",prefix:"the athlete will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the athlete will beat the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller jeels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the baker",prefix:"in the film studio, the baker is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the baker is vaking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host surveys the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he savg the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, he saves the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant turns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the student slipped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he stretched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the artist",prefix:"in an art class, the artist creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the artist creases a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"4cc8":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is watering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he is filling the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the soccer player",prefix:"on the playground, the soccer player tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the soccer player tasted the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy rides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the bookworm",prefix:"in the library, the bookworm is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the bookworm is reading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the athlete",prefix:"the athlete will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the athlete will break the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller mkilurs an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the baker",prefix:"in the film studio, the baker is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the baker is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host oulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he suehrged the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, he waves the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant burns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the student flipped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he sejt his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the artist",prefix:"in an art class, the artist hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the artist hokds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"4d05":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the gardener",prefix:"in the hotel, the gardener is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the gardener is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person is passing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, he",prefix:"in the restaurant, he ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, he ambdked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the cyclist",prefix:"in the park, the cyclist conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the cyclist conceals a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is managing the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"he feels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the photographer",prefix:"in the kitchen, the photographer is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the photographer is baking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the visitor",prefix:"at the entrance, the visitor pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the visitor pulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the guest",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the guest rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the guest rang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the speculator",prefix:"the speculator savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the speculator savrs the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, he",prefix:"in the darkness, he tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, he tjrns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, he",prefix:"in the exam, he sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, he sljpped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast sent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager holds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:44,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},5030:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the gardener",prefix:"in the hotel, the gardener is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the gardener is picking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person is habsdeing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, he",prefix:"in the restaurant, he licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, he licked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the cyclist",prefix:"in the park, the cyclist asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the cyclist asdafes a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is ujmnking the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will beat the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"he jeels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the photographer",prefix:"in the kitchen, the photographer is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the photographer is vaking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the visitor",prefix:"at the entrance, the visitor surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the visitor surveys the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the guest",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the guest savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the guest savg the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the speculator",prefix:"the speculator saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the speculator saves the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, he",prefix:"in the darkness, he turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, he turns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, he",prefix:"in the exam, he slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, he slipped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast stretched his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager creases a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},5455:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, he",prefix:"in the nursery, he is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, he is picking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, he",prefix:"before the interview, he is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, he is habsdeing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player licked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the spy",prefix:"on a mission, the spy asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the spy asdafes a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is ujmnking the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will beat the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller jeels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the baker",prefix:"the baker is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the baker is vaking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the host",prefix:"on a game show, the host surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the host surveys the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he savg the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, he",prefix:"in that fire, he saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, he saves the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the tenant turns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the student",prefix:"in the casino, the student slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the student slipped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he stretched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist creases a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"56d7":function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var i=n("2b0e"),o=n("7591"),r=n.n(o),a=n("3665"),s=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("Experiment",{attrs:{title:"Reading Experiment",translate:"no"}},[n("Screen",{staticClass:"instructions",attrs:{title:"Welcome",validations:{SubjectID:{minLength:e.$magpie.v.minLength(2)}}}},[n("div",{staticStyle:{width:"40em",margin:"auto"}},[n("div",{staticStyle:{"background-color":"lightgrey",padding:"10px"}},[n("b",[e._v(" Information About this Study ")])]),n("p",[n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What is being investigated?")]),e._v(" You are being asked to take part in a research study being done at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. This study will help us learn about how people read. It will take you around 20 minutes to complete. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("Who can participate?")]),e._v(" You can participate only if you are an adult native speaker of English. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What am I supposed to do as a participant?")]),e._v(" If you choose to be in the study, you will use the computer mouse to read sentences in English and answer questions about them. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What are my rights during participation?")]),e._v(" Your participation in this study is voluntary. If you choose to participate, you may change your mind and leave the study at any time by closing the web page. You do not have to provide reasons. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What risks and benefits can I expect?")]),e._v(" There are no foreseeable risks for participating in this study. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("Will I be compensated for participating?")]),e._v(" If you complete the experiment, you will be compensated for your time according to the amount specified on Prolific. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What data is collected from me and how is it used?")]),e._v(" During this study, we will track the position of your mouse on screen. At the end of the study you will be asked to complete a brief survey. No personally identifying information will be collected. The data from this study may be presented at scientific conferences and published in scientific journals, as well as in online repositories. All data will remain anonymous. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v(" Who reviewed this study? ")]),e._v(" This study's protocol has been approved by the MIT Committee on the Use of Humans as Experimental Subjects. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v(" Contact: ")]),e._v(" Please feel free to contact us anonymously via Prolific Direct Message. "),n("br")]),n("br"),n("div",{staticStyle:{"background-color":"lightgrey",padding:"10px"}},[n("b",[e._v(" Consent Form ")])]),n("br"),e._v(" I, the participant, confirm by clicking the button below: "),n("br"),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I have read and understood the study information above. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I comply with the inclusion and exclusion criteria for participation described above. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I have had enough time to decide about my participation. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I participate in this study voluntarily and consent that my personal data be used as described above. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I understand that I can stop participating at any moment. ")]),n("br"),n("tr",[n("td",[e._v("Please enter your Prolific ID to continue: ")]),n("td",[n("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID,expression:"$magpie.measurements.SubjectID"}],staticClass:"obligatory",attrs:{name:"TurkID",type:"text"},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"SubjectID",t.target.value)}}})])]),n("tr")]),e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID&&!e.$magpie.validateMeasurements.SubjectID.$invalid?n("div",[n("br"),e._v(" By clicking on the button below you consent to participating in this study: "),n("button",{on:{click:function(t){e.$magpie.addExpData({SubjectId:e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID}),e.$magpie.nextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Proceed ")])]):e._e()]),n("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Instructions"}},[n("p",[e._v(" In this study, you will read sentences. Unlike in normal reading, however, the texts will be blurred. In order to bring the text into focus, move your mouse over it. When you are done reading, click the 'Done Reading' button. ")])]),n("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Instructions"}},[n("p",[e._v(" As you read, you may notice that some of the sentences contain mistakes. An error could be a grammar error, typo, missing/extra words, etc. Please don't worry about punctuation or capitalization, which are not the focus of this study. ")]),n("p",[e._v(" After reading each sentence, you will be asked whether the sentence contained any mistakes. Indicate your choice by pressing the appropriate button. ")]),n("p",[e._v("Press the button to start the study.")])]),e._l(e.trials,(function(t,i){return[n("Screen",{key:i,staticClass:"main_screen",attrs:{progress:i/e.trials.length}},[n("Slide",[n("form",[n("input",{staticClass:"item_id",attrs:{type:"hidden"},domProps:{value:t.item_id}}),n("input",{staticClass:"experiment_id",attrs:{type:"hidden"},domProps:{value:t.experiment_id}}),n("input",{staticClass:"condition_id",attrs:{type:"hidden"},domProps:{value:t.condition_id}})]),n("div",{staticClass:"oval-cursor"}),[n("div",[e._v("Sentence "+e._s(i+1)+" of "+e._s(e.trials.length))])],e.showFirstDiv?n("div",{staticClass:"readingText",on:{mousemove:e.moveCursor,mouseleave:e.changeBack}},[e._l(t.text.split(" "),(function(t,i){return[n("span",{key:i,attrs:{"data-index":i}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t)+" ")])]}))],2):e._e(),n("div",{staticClass:"blurry-layer",staticStyle:{opacity:"0.3",filter:"blur(5px)",transition:"all 0.3s linear 0s"}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t.text)+" ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{height:"75px"}}),n("div",[e.showFirstDiv?n("button",{attrs:{disabled:!e.isCursorMoving},on:{click:e.toggleDivs}},[e._v(" Done Reading ")]):e._e()]),e.showFirstDiv?e._e():n("div",{staticClass:"userInput"},[n("p",[e._v(e._s(t.question))]),n("MultipleChoiceInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.response,options:[t.answer1,t.answer2]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"response",t)}}})],1),e.$magpie.measurements.response?n("button",{on:{click:function(n){e.toggleDivs();var o=e.$magpie.getAllData()[0].SubjectId;e.$magpie.addTrialData(Object.assign({},{TrialId:i,ItemId:t.item_id,Condition:t.condition_id,Experiment:t.experiment_id,TrialText:t.text,TrialType:"comprehensionQuestion",Question:t.question,Answer1:t.answer1,Answer2:t.answer2,userResponse:e.$magpie.measurements.response},t));var r=e.$magpie.getAllData(),a=r.filter((function(e){return Number(e.ItemId)===t.item_id&&e.Condition===t.condition_id}));a[0].SubjectId=o,e.$magpie.submitResults(e.$magpie.submissionUrl,a),e.$magpie.nextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Next Trial ")]):e._e()],2)],1)]})),n("Screen",[n("p",[e._v("1. Which input device are you using for this experiment?")]),n("MultipleChoiceInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.device,orientation:"horizontal",options:["Computer Mouse","Computer Trackpad","Other"]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"device",t)}}}),n("br"),n("br"),n("p",[e._v("2. Which hand are you using during this experiment?")]),n("MultipleChoiceInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.hand,orientation:"horizontal",options:["Left","Right","Both"]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"hand",t)}}}),n("br"),n("br"),n("p",[e._v(" What did you think about the experiment? Please describe how hard or easy the task felt, anything you noticed about the sentences, or any other thoughts you have. If anything was confusing or frustrating, please feel free to let us know! ")]),n("TextareaInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.response},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"response",t)}}}),n("button",{staticStyle:{bottom:"30%",transform:"translate(-50%, -50%)"},on:{click:function(t){return e.$magpie.saveAndNextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Submit ")])],1),n("Screen",[n("p",[e._v(" The next screen will submit your results and display your completion code. ")]),n("button",{staticStyle:{bottom:"30%",transform:"translate(-50%, -50%)"},on:{click:function(t){var n=e.$magpie.getAllData(),i=n[0].SubjectId,o=n[n.length-1],r=[Object.assign({},o,{SubjectId:i})];e.$magpie.submitResults(e.$magpie.submissionUrl,r),e.$magpie.nextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Continue ")])]),n("Screen",{attrs:{title:"Study Complete"}},[n("p",{staticClass:"selectable-text",staticStyle:{"font-size":"24px"}},[e._v("Completion Code:")]),n("p",{staticClass:"selectable-text",staticStyle:{"font-size":"24px"}},[e._v("C101RMLG")])])],2)},c=[],d=n("aed0"),h=n.n(d),l=n("2ef0"),_=n.n(l),u=n("0c75"),b=n.n(u),p=n("9ac0"),m=n.n(p),w=n("ee1a"),g=n.n(w),x=n("b358"),v=n.n(x),f=n("76e5"),j=n.n(f),k=n("1bf7"),q=n.n(k),y=n("31bc"),I=n.n(y),D=n("8bc4"),W=n.n(D),C=n("28de"),P=n.n(C),Y=n("4149"),N=n.n(Y),S=n("8316"),O=n.n(S),$=n("5455"),T=n.n($),M=n("2c35"),L=n.n(M),A=n("5ac5"),E=n.n(A),R=n("b0f8"),F=n.n(R),U=n("1cfa"),B=n.n(U),z=n("5030"),X=n.n(z),H=n("8f6f"),G=n.n(H),J=n("4cc8"),Q=n.n(J),K=n("0c1a"),V=n.n(K),Z=n("81b2"),ee=n.n(Z),te=n("b1ea"),ne=n.n(te),ie=n("ba7d"),oe=n.n(ie),re=n("3010"),ae=n.n(re),se=n("93de"),ce=n.n(se),de=n("0309"),he=n.n(de),le=n("77bf"),_e=n.n(le),ue=n("7a17"),be=n.n(ue),pe=n("9995"),me=n.n(pe),we=n("7a49"),ge=n.n(we),xe=n("9fab"),ve=n.n(xe),fe=n("d62e"),je=n.n(fe),ke=n("086f"),qe=n.n(ke),ye=n("fab3"),Ie=n.n(ye),De=n("6495"),We=n.n(De),Ce=n("95c5"),Pe=n.n(Ce),Ye=n("cb70"),Ne=n.n(Ye),Se=n("2ffb"),Oe=n.n(Se),$e=n("c182"),Te=n.n($e),Me=n("f71e"),Le=n.n(Me),Ae=n("a020"),Ee=n.n(Ae),Re=n("e4ac"),Fe=n.n(Re),Ue=n("660e"),Be=n.n(Ue),ze=n("4d05"),Xe=n.n(ze),He=n("3660"),Ge=n.n(He);const Je=new URLSearchParams(window.location.search);console.log(Je);const Qe=Je.get("LIST_ID")||"1";console.log(Qe);const Ke=Qe.padStart(2,"0"),Ve={"01":b.a,"02":m.a,"03":g.a,"04":v.a,"05":j.a,"06":q.a,"07":I.a,"08":W.a,"09":P.a,10:N.a,11:O.a,12:T.a,13:L.a,14:E.a,15:F.a,16:B.a,17:X.a,18:G.a,19:Q.a,20:V.a,21:ee.a,22:ne.a,23:oe.a,24:ae.a,25:ce.a,26:he.a,27:_e.a,28:be.a,29:me.a,30:ge.a,31:ve.a,32:je.a,33:qe.a,34:Ie.a,35:We.a,36:Pe.a,37:Ne.a,38:Oe.a,39:Te.a,40:Le.a,41:Ee.a,42:Fe.a,43:Be.a,44:Xe.a,45:Ge.a},Ze=Ve[Ke]||b.a;var et={name:"App",data(){const e=!1;console.log(Ze);const t=_.a.shuffle(Ze).map((e,t)=>({...e,item_id:e["Item"],text:e["sentence"],experiment_id:"ncprediction",verb_condition:e["verb_condition"],verb:e["verb"],subject_condition:e["subject_condition"],subject:e["subject"],context_condition:e["context_condition"],context:e["context"],predicate_condition:e["predicate_condition"],predicate:e["predicate"],Preamble:e["Preamble"],prefix:e["prefix"],CriticalWord:e["CriticalWord"],intervention_simple:e["intervention_simple"],continuation:e["continuation"],aux:e["aux"],verb_1_o:e["verb_1_o"],question:e["question"],group_id:e["group_id"],answer1:e["answer1"],answer2:e["answer2"],question_delay:e["question_delay"],correct_answer:e["correct_answer"],with_question:e["with_question"],material_id:e["material_id"]})),n=h.a.map((e,t)=>({item_id:e["Item"],text:e["Sentence"],condition_id:"filler",experiment_id:"ncprediction",with_question:e["with_question"],question:e["question"],answer1:e["answer1"],answer2:e["answer2"],correct_answer:e["correct_answer"],question_delay:e["question_delay"]})),i=n.splice(6,5),o=i.concat(_.a.shuffle(t.concat(n)));return console.log(o),{isCursorMoving:!1,trials:o,currentIndex:null,showFirstDiv:!0,mousePosition:{x:0,y:0},userResponse:"",showImages:e}},computed:{console:()=>console,window:()=>window},mounted(){setInterval(this.saveData,50)},methods:{changeBack(){this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.remove("grow"),this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.remove("blank"),this.currentIndex=null},saveData(){if(null!==this.currentIndex){const e=this.$el.querySelector(`span[data-index="${this.currentIndex}"]`);if(e){const t=e.getBoundingClientRect();$magpie.addTrialData({Experiment:this.$el.querySelector(".experiment_id").value,Condition:this.$el.querySelector(".condition_id").value,ItemId:this.$el.querySelector(".item_id").value,Index:this.currentIndex,Word:e.innerHTML,mousePositionX:this.mousePosition.x,mousePositionY:this.mousePosition.y,wordPositionTop:t.top,wordPositionLeft:t.left,wordPositionBottom:t.bottom,wordPositionRight:t.right})}else $magpie.addTrialData({Experiment:this.$el.querySelector(".experiment_id").value,Condition:this.$el.querySelector(".condition_id").value,ItemId:this.$el.querySelector(".item_id").value,Index:this.currentIndex,mousePositionX:this.mousePosition.x,mousePositionY:this.mousePosition.y})}},moveCursor(e){this.isCursorMoving=!0,this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.add("grow");let t=e.clientX,n=e.clientY;const i=document.elementFromPoint(t,n).closest("span");if(i)this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.remove("blank"),this.currentIndex=i.getAttribute("data-index");else{this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.add("blank");const e=document.elementFromPoint(t,n-3).closest("span");this.currentIndex=e?e.getAttribute("data-index"):-1}this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").style.left=t+12+"px",this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").style.top=n-6+"px",this.mousePosition.x=e.clientX,this.mousePosition.y=e.clientY},toggleDivs(){this.showFirstDiv=!this.showFirstDiv,this.isCursorMoving=!1},getScreenDimensions(){return{window_inner_width:window.innerWidth,window_inner_height:window.innerHeight}}}},tt=et,nt=(n("d9a9"),n("2877")),it=Object(nt["a"])(tt,s,c,!1,null,null,null),ot=it.exports,rt={experimentId:"108",serverUrl:"https://noisy-comp-server-311aa565092d.herokuapp.com",socketUrl:"wss://noisy-comp-server-311aa565092d.herokuapp.com/socket",completionUrl:"https://app.prolific.com/submissions/complete?cc=C101RMLG",contactEmail:"thclark@mit.edu",mode:"directLink",language:"en"};i["default"].config.productionTip=!1,i["default"].use(r.a,{prefix:"Canvas"}),i["default"].use(a["a"],rt),new i["default"]({render:e=>e(ot)}).$mount("#app")},"5ac5":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the traveler",prefix:"in the hotel, the traveler is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the traveler is picking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the applicant",prefix:"the applicant is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the applicant is habsdeing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth licked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he asdafes a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the coach",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the coach is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the coach is ujmnking the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, he",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, he will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, he will beat the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"the man rushing to catch a train jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the man rushing to catch a train jeels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is vaking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he surveys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour savg the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter saves the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the match",prefix:"in the darkness, the match turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the match turns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the gambler",prefix:"in the exam, the gambler slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the gambler slipped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman stretched his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he creases a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},6495:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the gardener",prefix:"in the hotel, the gardener is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the gardener is pjcking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person is killing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, he",prefix:"in the restaurant, he jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, he jicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the cyclist",prefix:"in the park, the cyclist hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the cyclist hides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is leading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will besr the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"he peels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the photographer",prefix:"in the kitchen, the photographer is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the photographer is taking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the visitor",prefix:"at the entrance, the visitor hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the visitor hugjds the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the guest",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the guest sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the guest sang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the speculator",prefix:"the speculator brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the speculator brandishes the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, he",prefix:"in the darkness, he lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, he lights the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, he",prefix:"in the exam, he tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, he tossed a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast asdfaed his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:35,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"660e":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the bored person",prefix:"on the train, the bored person is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the bored person is passing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he ambdked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist conceals a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is managing the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the leader",prefix:"the leader will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the leader will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, he",prefix:"in the waiting line, he feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, he feels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the photographer",prefix:"in the film studio, the photographer is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the photographer is baking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor pulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest rang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the speculator",prefix:"at the post office, the speculator savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the speculator savrs the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, he",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, he tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, he tjrns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"he sljpped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the gymnast",prefix:"in the dance studio, the gymnast sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the gymnast sent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the manager",prefix:"in an art class, the manager holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the manager holds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:43,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"76e5":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the traveler",prefix:"in the hotel, the traveler is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the traveler is packing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the applicant",prefix:"the applicant is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the applicant is fillibg the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth kicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he rkdes a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the coach",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the coach is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the coach is revding the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, he",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, he will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, he will bear the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"the man rushing to catch a train experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the man rushing to catch a train experiences an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is cooking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he polls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour pressed the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the match",prefix:"in the darkness, the match jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the match jubkls the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the gambler",prefix:"in the exam, the gambler ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the gambler ajifoased a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman bent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he folds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"77bf":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the gardener",prefix:"in the nursery, the gardener is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the gardener is watering the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the bored person",prefix:"before the interview, the bored person is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the bored person is filling the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he tasted the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the cyclist",prefix:"on a mission, the cyclist rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the cyclist rides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is reading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will break the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, he",prefix:"in the fruit market, he mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, he mkilurs an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the visitor",prefix:"on a game show, the visitor oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the visitor oulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest suehrged the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the speculator",prefix:"in that fire, the speculator waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the speculator waves the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"he burns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, he",prefix:"in the casino, he flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, he flipped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the gymnast",prefix:"at the post office, the gymnast sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the gymnast sejt his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager hokds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:27,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"7a17":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is pjcking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he is killing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the soccer player",prefix:"on the playground, the soccer player jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the soccer player jicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy hides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the bookworm",prefix:"in the library, the bookworm is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the bookworm is leading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the athlete",prefix:"the athlete will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the athlete will besr the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller peels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the baker",prefix:"in the film studio, the baker is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the baker is taking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host hugjds the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he sang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, he brandishes the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant lights the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the student tossed a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he asdfaed his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the artist",prefix:"in an art class, the artist jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the artist jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:28,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"7a49":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, he",prefix:"in the nursery, he is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, he is pjcking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, he",prefix:"before the interview, he is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, he is killing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player jicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the spy",prefix:"on a mission, the spy hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the spy hides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is leading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will besr the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller peels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the baker",prefix:"the baker is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the baker is taking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the host",prefix:"on a game show, the host hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the host hugjds the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he sang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, he",prefix:"in that fire, he brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, he brandishes the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the tenant lights the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the student",prefix:"in the casino, the student tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the student tossed a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he asdfaed his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:30,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"81b2":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, he",prefix:"in the nursery, he is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, he is watering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, he",prefix:"before the interview, he is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, he is filling the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player tasted the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the spy",prefix:"on a mission, the spy rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the spy rides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is reading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will break the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller mkilurs an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the baker",prefix:"the baker is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the baker is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the host",prefix:"on a game show, the host oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the host oulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he suehrged the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, he",prefix:"in that fire, he waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, he waves the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the tenant burns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the student",prefix:"in the casino, the student flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the student flipped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he sejt his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist hokds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},8316:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is picking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he is habsdeing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the soccer player",prefix:"in the restaurant, the soccer player licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the soccer player licked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the spy",prefix:"in the park, the spy asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the spy asdafes a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is ujmnking the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will beat the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the fruit seller",prefix:"the fruit seller jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the fruit seller jeels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the baker",prefix:"in the kitchen, the baker is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the baker is vaking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the host",prefix:"at the entrance, the host surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the host surveys the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, he",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, he savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, he savg the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he saves the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the tenant",prefix:"in the darkness, the tenant turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the tenant turns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the student",prefix:"in the exam, the student slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the student slipped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he stretched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the artist",prefix:"the artist creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the artist creases a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"8bc4":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the gardener",prefix:"in the hotel, the gardener is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the gardener is packing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person is fillibg the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, he",prefix:"in the restaurant, he kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, he kicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the cyclist",prefix:"in the park, the cyclist rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the cyclist rkdes a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is revding the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the leader will bear the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"he experiences an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the photographer",prefix:"in the kitchen, the photographer is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the photographer is cooking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the visitor",prefix:"at the entrance, the visitor polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the visitor polls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the guest",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the guest pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the guest pressed the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the speculator",prefix:"the speculator jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the speculator jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, he",prefix:"in the darkness, he jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, he jubkls the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, he",prefix:"in the exam, he ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, he ajifoased a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast bent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager folds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"8f6f":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the gardener",prefix:"in the nursery, the gardener is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the gardener is picking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the bored person",prefix:"before the interview, the bored person is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the bored person is habsdeing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he licked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the cyclist",prefix:"on a mission, the cyclist asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the cyclist asdafes a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is ujmnking the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will beat the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, he",prefix:"in the fruit market, he jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, he jeels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is vaking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the visitor",prefix:"on a game show, the visitor surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the visitor surveys the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest savg the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the speculator",prefix:"in that fire, the speculator saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the speculator saves the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"he turns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, he",prefix:"in the casino, he slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, he slipped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the gymnast",prefix:"at the post office, the gymnast stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the gymnast stretched his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager creases a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"93de":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is watering the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the bored person",prefix:"on the train, the bored person is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the bored person is filling the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he tasted the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist rides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is reading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the leader",prefix:"the leader will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the leader will break the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, he",prefix:"in the waiting line, he mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, he mkilurs an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the photographer",prefix:"in the film studio, the photographer is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the photographer is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor oulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest suehrged the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the speculator",prefix:"at the post office, the speculator waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the speculator waves the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, he",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, he burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, he burns the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"he flipped a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the gymnast",prefix:"in the dance studio, the gymnast sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the gymnast sejt his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the manager",prefix:"in an art class, the manager hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the manager hokds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:25,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"95c5":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the gardener",prefix:"in the nursery, the gardener is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the gardener is pjcking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the bored person",prefix:"before the interview, the bored person is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the bored person is killing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he jicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the cyclist",prefix:"on a mission, the cyclist hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the cyclist hides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is leading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the leader will besr the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, he",prefix:"in the fruit market, he peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, he peels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is taking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the visitor",prefix:"on a game show, the visitor hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the visitor hugjds the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest sang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the speculator",prefix:"in that fire, the speculator brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the speculator brandishes the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"he lights the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, he",prefix:"in the casino, he tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, he tossed a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the gymnast",prefix:"at the post office, the gymnast asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the gymnast asdfaed his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the manager jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:36,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},9995:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is pjcking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he is killing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the soccer player",prefix:"in the restaurant, the soccer player jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the soccer player jicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the spy",prefix:"in the park, the spy hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the spy hides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is leading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will besr the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the fruit seller",prefix:"the fruit seller peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the fruit seller peels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the baker",prefix:"in the kitchen, the baker is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the baker is taking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the host",prefix:"at the entrance, the host hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the host hugjds the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, he",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, he sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, he sang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he brandishes the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the tenant",prefix:"in the darkness, the tenant lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the tenant lights the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the student",prefix:"in the exam, the student tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the student tossed a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he asdfaed his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the artist",prefix:"the artist jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the artist jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:29,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"9ac0":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is packing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he is fillibg the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the soccer player",prefix:"in the restaurant, the soccer player kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the soccer player kicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, the spy",prefix:"in the park, the spy rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, the spy rkdes a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the bookworm is revding the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, the athlete will bear the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the fruit seller",prefix:"the fruit seller experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the fruit seller experiences an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, the baker",prefix:"in the kitchen, the baker is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, the baker is cooking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, the host",prefix:"at the entrance, the host polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, the host polls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, he",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, he pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, he pressed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the tenant",prefix:"in the darkness, the tenant jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the tenant jubkls the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the student",prefix:"in the exam, the student ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the student ajifoased a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he bent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the artist",prefix:"the artist folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the artist folds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},"9fab":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is pjcking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the applicant",prefix:"on the train, the applicant is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the applicant is killing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth jicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he hides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the coach",prefix:"in the library, the coach is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the coach is leading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"he will besr the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train peels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is taking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he hugjds the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour sang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the firefighter",prefix:"at the post office, the firefighter brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the firefighter brandishes the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the match",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the match lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the match lights the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the gambler",prefix:"the gambler tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the gambler tossed a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the mailman",prefix:"in the dance studio, the mailman asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the mailman asdfaed his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, he",prefix:"in an art class, he jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, he jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:31,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},a020:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the traveler",prefix:"in the hotel, the traveler is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the traveler is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the applicant",prefix:"the applicant is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the applicant is passing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth ambdked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he conceals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the coach",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the coach is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the coach is managing the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, he",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, he will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, he will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"the man rushing to catch a train feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the man rushing to catch a train feels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is baking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he pulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour rang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter savrs the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the match",prefix:"in the darkness, the match tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the match tjrns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the gambler",prefix:"in the exam, the gambler sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the gambler sljpped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman sent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he holds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:41,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},aed0:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,Sentence:"the bird sang beautifully",with_question:!0,question:"Did the bird sing?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:2,Sentence:"children played exciting games",with_question:!0,question:"Did the children play games?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:3,Sentence:"flowers bloom during spring",with_question:!0,question:"Do flowers bloom in spring?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:4,Sentence:"the movie entertained many people",with_question:!0,question:"Did the movie entertain people?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:5,Sentence:"on the table, the book lay open",with_question:!0,question:"Was the book on the table?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:6,Sentence:"the computer works perfectly",with_question:!0,question:"Does the computer work well?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:7,Sentence:"in the café, people relax quietly",with_question:!0,question:"Do people relax in the café?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:8,Sentence:"tourists watched the sunset",with_question:!0,question:"Did tourists watch the sunset?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:9,Sentence:"music helps tired workers",with_question:!0,question:"Does music help workers?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:10,Sentence:"the flowers attract busy bees",with_question:!0,question:"Do the flowers attract bees?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:11,Sentence:"the cashier smiled warmly",with_question:!0,question:"Did the cashier smile?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:12,Sentence:"during dinner, the family laughed together",with_question:!0,question:"Did the family laugh during dinner?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:13,Sentence:"the professor explained the theory",with_question:!0,question:"Did the professor explain something?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:14,Sentence:"the artist painted colorful pictures",with_question:!0,question:"Did the artist paint pictures?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:15,Sentence:"at the concert, the musician performed brilliantly",with_question:!0,question:"Did the musician perform at the concert?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0}]},b0f8:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the traveler",prefix:"in the nursery, the traveler is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the traveler is picking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is habsdeing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the applicant",prefix:"before the interview, the applicant is habsdeing the",CriticalWord:"is habsdeing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the applicant is habsdeing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth licked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdafes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he asdafes a",CriticalWord:"asdafes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he asdafes a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is ujmnking the",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is ujmnking the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"will beat",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will beat the",CriticalWord:"will beat",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will beat the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jeels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train jeels an",CriticalWord:"jeels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train jeels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is vaking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is vaking a",CriticalWord:"is vaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is vaking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he surveys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savg",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour savg the",CriticalWord:"savg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour savg the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saves",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the firefighter",prefix:"in that fire, the firefighter saves the",CriticalWord:"saves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the firefighter saves the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"turns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the match",prefix:"the match turns the",CriticalWord:"turns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the match turns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"slipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the gambler",prefix:"in the casino, the gambler slipped a",CriticalWord:"slipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the gambler slipped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the mailman",prefix:"at the post office, the mailman stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the mailman stretched his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he creases a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},b1ea:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is watering the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the applicant",prefix:"on the train, the applicant is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the applicant is filling the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth tasted the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he rides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the coach",prefix:"in the library, the coach is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the coach is reading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"he will break the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train mkilurs an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he oulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour suehrged the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the firefighter",prefix:"at the post office, the firefighter waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the firefighter waves the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the match",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the match burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the match burns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the gambler",prefix:"the gambler flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the gambler flipped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the mailman",prefix:"in the dance studio, the mailman sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the mailman sejt his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, he",prefix:"in an art class, he hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, he hokds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},b358:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is packing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the applicant",prefix:"on the train, the applicant is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the applicant is fillibg the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth kicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he rkdes a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the coach",prefix:"in the library, the coach is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the coach is revding the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"he will bear the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train experiences an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is cooking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he polls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour pressed the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the firefighter",prefix:"at the post office, the firefighter jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the firefighter jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the match",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the match jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the match jubkls the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the gambler",prefix:"the gambler ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the gambler ajifoased a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the mailman",prefix:"in the dance studio, the mailman bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the mailman bent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, he",prefix:"in an art class, he folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, he folds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},ba7d:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the traveler",prefix:"in the hotel, the traveler is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the traveler is watering the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is filling",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the applicant",prefix:"the applicant is filling the",CriticalWord:"is filling",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the applicant is filling the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth tasted the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he rides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the coach",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the coach is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the coach is reading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"will break",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, he",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, he will break the",CriticalWord:"will break",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, he will break the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mkilurs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"the man rushing to catch a train mkilurs an",CriticalWord:"mkilurs",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the man rushing to catch a train mkilurs an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ujmnking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is ujmnking a",CriticalWord:"is ujmnking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is ujmnking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he oulls the",CriticalWord:"oulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he oulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"suehrged",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour suehrged the",CriticalWord:"suehrged",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour suehrged the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waves",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter waves the",CriticalWord:"waves",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter waves the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"burns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the match",prefix:"in the darkness, the match burns the",CriticalWord:"burns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the match burns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"flipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the gambler",prefix:"in the exam, the gambler flipped a",CriticalWord:"flipped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the gambler flipped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sejt",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman sejt his",CriticalWord:"sejt",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman sejt his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"hokds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he hokds a",CriticalWord:"hokds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he hokds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},c182:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, he",prefix:"in the nursery, he is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, he is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, he",prefix:"before the interview, he is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, he is passing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player ambdked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the spy",prefix:"on a mission, the spy conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the spy conceals a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is managing the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller feels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the baker",prefix:"the baker is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the baker is baking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the host",prefix:"on a game show, the host pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the host pulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he rang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, he",prefix:"in that fire, he savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, he savrs the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the tenant tjrns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the student",prefix:"in the casino, the student sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the student sljpped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he sent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist holds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:39,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},cb70:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he is passing the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the soccer player",prefix:"on the playground, the soccer player ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the soccer player ambdked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy conceals a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the bookworm",prefix:"in the library, the bookworm is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the bookworm is managing the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the athlete",prefix:"the athlete will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the athlete will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the fruit seller feels an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the baker",prefix:"in the film studio, the baker is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the baker is baking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host pulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he rang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, he savrs the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the tenant tjrns the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the student sljpped a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he sent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the artist",prefix:"in an art class, the artist holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the artist holds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:37,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},d62e:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, the traveler",prefix:"in the hotel, the traveler is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, the traveler is pjcking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"the applicant",prefix:"the applicant is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the applicant is killing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the restaurant, the child with a sweet tooth jicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he hides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, the coach",prefix:"after the manager resigned, the coach is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, the coach is leading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when confronted by the challenge, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"when confronted by the challenge, he",prefix:"when confronted by the challenge, he will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"when confronted by the challenge, he will besr the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"the man rushing to catch a train peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"the man rushing to catch a train peels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is taking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he hugjds the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context2",context:"arriving at the front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour",prefix:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"arriving at the front desk, the troubadour sang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter brandishes the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the darkness, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"in the darkness, the match",prefix:"in the darkness, the match lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"in the darkness, the match lights the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the exam, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the exam, the gambler",prefix:"in the exam, the gambler tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the exam, the gambler tossed a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman asdfaed his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:32,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},d725:function(e,t,n){},d9a9:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n("d725")},e4ac:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, the traveler",prefix:"in the nursery, the traveler is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, the traveler is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, the applicant",prefix:"before the interview, the applicant is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, the applicant is passing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth ambdked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he conceals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is managing the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, he will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the man rushing to catch a train feels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is baking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he pulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour rang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, the firefighter",prefix:"in that fire, the firefighter savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, the firefighter savrs the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the match",prefix:"the match tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the match tjrns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the gambler",prefix:"in the casino, the gambler sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the gambler sljpped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, the mailman",prefix:"at the post office, the mailman sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, the mailman sent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he holds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:42,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},ee1a:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the nursery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the nursery, he",prefix:"in the nursery, he is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the nursery, he is packing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is fillibg",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before the interview, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"before the interview, he",prefix:"before the interview, he is fillibg the",CriticalWord:"is fillibg",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before the interview, he is fillibg the form",question:"Is he filling the form?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player kicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"rkdes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, the spy",prefix:"on a mission, the spy rkdes a",CriticalWord:"rkdes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, the spy rkdes a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is revding",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is revding the",CriticalWord:"is revding",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is revding the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"will bear",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the athlete",context_condition:"context2",context:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete",prefix:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will bear the",CriticalWord:"will bear",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"in tomorrow's Olympic game, the athlete will bear the responsibility",question:"Will the athlete bear the responsibility?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"experiences",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the fruit seller",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the fruit market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller",prefix:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller experiences an",CriticalWord:"experiences",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the fruit market, the fruit seller experiences an orange",question:"Does the fruit seller peel an orange?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the baker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the baker",prefix:"the baker is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the baker is cooking a photo",question:"Is the baker taking a photo?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, the host",prefix:"on a game show, the host polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, the host polls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he pressed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jiasodhuos",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in that fire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"in that fire, he",prefix:"in that fire, he jiasodhuos the",CriticalWord:"jiasodhuos",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"in that fire, he jiasodhuos the person",question:"Does he save the person?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jubkls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant jubkls the",CriticalWord:"jubkls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"the tenant jubkls the key",question:"Does the tenant turn the key?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ajifoased",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the casino, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"in the casino, the student",prefix:"in the casino, the student ajifoased a",CriticalWord:"ajifoased",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"in the casino, the student ajifoased a note",question:"Did the student slip a note?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he bent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the artist",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, the artist folds a meeting",question:"Does the artist hold a meeting?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},f71e:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ajiaeasing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is ajiaeasing the",CriticalWord:"is ajiaeasing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is ajiaeasing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is passing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the applicant",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the applicant",prefix:"on the train, the applicant is passing the",CriticalWord:"is passing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the applicant is passing the form",question:"Is the applicant filling the form?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ambdked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth ambdked the",CriticalWord:"ambdked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, the child with a sweet tooth ambdked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he conceals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, the coach",prefix:"in the library, the coach is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, the coach is managing the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"will aasoidjoi",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he will aasoidjoi the",CriticalWord:"will aasoidjoi",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"he will aasoidjoi the responsibility",question:"Will he bear the responsibility?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"feels",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the man rushing to catch a train",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train",prefix:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train feels an",CriticalWord:"feels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, the man rushing to catch a train feels an orange",question:"Does the man rushing to catch a train peel an orange?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is baking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he pulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the troubadour rang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"savrs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the firefighter",prefix:"at the post office, the firefighter savrs the",CriticalWord:"savrs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the firefighter savrs the person",question:"Does the firefighter save the person?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tjrns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the match",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, the match",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, the match tjrns the",CriticalWord:"tjrns",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, the match tjrns the key",question:"Does the match turn the key?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sljpped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gambler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"the gambler",prefix:"the gambler sljpped a",CriticalWord:"sljpped",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"the gambler sljpped a note",question:"Did the gambler slip a note?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the mailman",prefix:"in the dance studio, the mailman sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the mailman sent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, he",prefix:"in an art class, he holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, he holds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:40,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]},fab3:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is pjcking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is pjcking the",CriticalWord:"is pjcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is pjcking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:10},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is killing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"form",Preamble:"on the train, the bored person",prefix:"on the train, the bored person is killing the",CriticalWord:"is killing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"form",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, the bored person is killing the form",question:"Is the bored person filling the form?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:12},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he jicked the",CriticalWord:"jicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he jicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:1},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist hides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:14},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is leading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:6},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"will besr",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the leader",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"responsibility",Preamble:"the leader",prefix:"the leader will besr the",CriticalWord:"will besr",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"responsibility",aux:"Will",verb_1_o:"bear",sentence:"the leader will besr the responsibility",question:"Will the leader bear the responsibility?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:9},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"peels",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the waiting line, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"orange",Preamble:"in the waiting line, he",prefix:"in the waiting line, he peels an",CriticalWord:"peels",intervention_simple:"an",continuation:"orange",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"peel",sentence:"in the waiting line, he peels an orange",question:"Does he peel an orange?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:3},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, the photographer",prefix:"in the film studio, the photographer is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, the photographer is taking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:2},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hugjds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor hugjds the",CriticalWord:"hugjds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor hugjds the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:15},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, the guest sang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:5},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the speculator",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the post office, the speculator",prefix:"at the post office, the speculator brandishes the",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"person",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the post office, the speculator brandishes the person",question:"Does the speculator save the person?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:8},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"lights",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"outside the apartment entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"key",Preamble:"outside the apartment entrance, he",prefix:"outside the apartment entrance, he lights the",CriticalWord:"lights",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"key",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"turn",sentence:"outside the apartment entrance, he lights the key",question:"Does he turn the key?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:11},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tossed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"note",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tossed a",CriticalWord:"tossed",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"note",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"slip",sentence:"he tossed a note",question:"Did he slip a note?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"asdfaed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, the gymnast",prefix:"in the dance studio, the gymnast asdfaed his",CriticalWord:"asdfaed",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, the gymnast asdfaed his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:4},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jsaideafs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"context2",context:"in an art class, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"in an art class, the manager",prefix:"in an art class, the manager jsaideafs a",CriticalWord:"jsaideafs",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"in an art class, the manager jsaideafs a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:34,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:!0,material_id:7}]}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.82c19267.js.map